Join me at Mariners Huntington Beach if you live in the area. You can learn more through the link below. On April 22nd, we'll begin a course created by Inez Franklin and Steve Bang Lee from our Deep Dive series called The Image of God. Together, we'll explore the scriptural meaning and application of God's image being reflected in every single person.
being three-time Golden Globe winning actor Jim Carrey. Because then I would be enough. It would finally be true. And I could stop this terrible search for what I know ultimately won't fulfill me.
and a time to throw away. It's a time for your annual garage sale. A time to tear and a time to sow. A time to be silent and a time to speak.
Is this? I have seven marbles left before she graduates high school. That's how fast that time goes. It just continually comes our way.
made everything appropriate in its time. He has put eternity in their hearts, but no one can discover the work God has done from beginning to end. I know that there is nothing better for them to rejoice and enjoy the good life. It is also the gift of God whenever anyone eats, drinks, and enjoys all his efforts.
boxes that he wrestles with in this text. I had dinner with some friends recently. My wife Kay and I had dinner with some friends. And we were just talking about this stage in life with a kid graduating high school and moving out of the home and same time losing a parent.
Life, how can we find meaning in all of the times that are thrust upon us? How can we find meaning in the paradoxes and the messiness and the complexity of life? Where do we find meaning? There's three verses in the middle of Ecclesiastes 3 that are just so beautiful that will help you see meaning in all of the times that are thrust upon you in life.
apparent, there's no pain like seeing your kids in pain. And so it was a really painful season. And then now I look and she's about to graduate high school and she loves school. She's excited about college.
So that when you realize that nothing else in this world will satisfy you through all of the times, all of the seasons that you lived through in life, that you will look to him and be in awe of him. Augustine, the early church father, he talked about how one night when he was a young adult and he was a young man, he was with a group of friends in Rome. And this is in his very famous work, The Confessions. They were walking through the streets of Rome.
the less you would allow anything that was not you to grow sweet to me. It's amazing what he's saying. God, I thought you were mocking me, but you were actually being really kind because you didn't allow creative things to satisfy me. Because if creative things had really satisfied me, then I wouldn't have looked to you.